[{"answer": " You have so many nice jackets. I don't know why you had to bring this jacket. Who wears a jacket like this?  What's wrong with that nice gray one? You have beautiful clothes. They sit in your closet. my friend, you can't wear", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pony-Remark.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I thought you were getting it", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Should I pick up", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pony-Remark.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I'll get it", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You want me to get that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pony-Remark.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I'll get it!", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I don't know her either.  She makes me fly all the way from Floriday for this, and then she criticizes my jacket", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pony-Remark.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "How come he gets to leave", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What are you doing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pony-Remark.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Levels", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "When do you intend to do this", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pony-Remark.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You're doing this yourself", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You're doing this yourself", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pony-Remark.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Oh, no. It's not that I don't think you can. I know that you can't, and I'm positive that you won't", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pony-Remark.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " These peas are bursting with countr", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Horses. They're like big riding dogs", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pony-Remark.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I know, I hated those kids. In fact, I hate anyone that ever had a pony when they were growing up", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "So, when do I get my dinner", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pony-Remark.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Yes. I know you're not gonna do it. That's why I bet", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "There's no dinner. The bet's off. I'm not gonna do it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pony-Remark.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "There's not bet if I' not doing it", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yes. I know you're not gonna do it. That's why I bet", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pony-Remark.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "That's the bet! That you're not doing it", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yeah, well, I could do it. I don't want to do it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pony-Remark.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "And it could be done", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "We didn't bet on if you wanted to. We bet on if it would be done", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pony-Remark.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Well, of course it could be done! Anything could be done! But it only is done if it's done. Show me the levels! The bet is the levels", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What? Nothing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pony-Remark.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Oh, don't be ridiculous. She was an old woman", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Oh no, no, no. She forgot all about that. She was much mor upset about the potato salad", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pony-Remark.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Yeah, my brother lives there. I think my friend would've liked that place", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Oh, you can have mine. I'll ship it out ot you.. but what about that big apartment on West End Avenue", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pony-Remark.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Dry, wet.. what's happening with your apartment", "qsentId": 34}]